No, no, no, no. What do we need at events?
People.
We saw during the pandemic, so many people
were afraid that live events would not come back,
because it's more convenient to watch it online.
It's more convenient to watch it at your own pace.
But we as human beings are social creatures.
We desire that connection.
We desire that interaction.
We want to be there.
We want to feel the excitement.
Can you imagine trying to get hyped before a
conference keynote session from your computer at home?
Like the vibe in the general session room this morning.
It is much more difficult to create that level
of excitement, of hype, if they're not here together.
There is a term that we use in academia,
and it's called communitas.
It means people coming together.
There is a certain aspect of events that gives us the
opportunity to remove the barriers that keep us
separated in day-to-day lives.
When you're standing in line to get one of the super
fancy yummy burgers in the exhibit hall,
and you're just chatting somebody up, you're not
thinking about, oh, this is a CEO,
or this is somebody that makes more money than me
or less money than me, or they don't have kids and I do.
You're not thinking about that.
You are here in the moment,
enjoying the moment with other people.